var data = [
  {
    category: "Cricket",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "Which year India won ODI and T20 world cups ?",
        answer: "ODI - 1983 and 2011 <br/> T20 - 2007"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question:
          "Who was the player of tournament in 2015 cricket world cup ?",
        answer: "Mitchell Starc for 22 wickets"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question:
          "Who is the leading wicket taker in test cricker? How many wickets he took?",
        answer: "Muttiah Muralitharan, 800 wickets"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question:
          "Name all the cricketers who scored double centuary in ODI (Name 4 out of 5)",
        answer:
          "Sachin Tendulkar, Virender Sehwag, Rohit Sharma, Chris Gayle and Martin Guptill"
      },
      {
        points: 500,
        question:
          "How many matches did it take for Sachin to score his first ODI century ?",
        answer: "79"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category: "Logic ?",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question:
          "Everyone in the world needs it, but they usually give it without taking it. What is it ?",
        answer: "Advice"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question:
          "I am an odd number. Take away one letter and I become even. What number am I ?",
        answer: "Seven (take away 's' and it becomes even)"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "What gets sharper the more you use it ?",
        answer: "Your brain"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question:
          "What belongs to you but gets used by everyone else more than you ?",
        answer: "Your name"
      },
      {
        points: 500,
        question: "What never asks a question but gets answered all the time ?",
        answer: "google search engine"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    category: "GENERAL KNOWLEDGE",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "Who is current chief minister of uttar pradesh?",
        answer: "Yogi Adityanath"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "Which city in US is known as city of Silicon Hills ?",
        answer: "Austin"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "What is currency of Russia ?",
        answer: "Ruble"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question: "India has how many states ?",
        answer: "29"
      },
      {
        points: 500,
        question: "How many Oz are there in one liter ?",
        answer: "33.814. Full points for 33"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    category: "CORPORATE",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "Who is current CEO of Alphabet ?",
        answer: "Sundar Pichai"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "What is the tag line of walmart?",
        answer: "Save money, live better"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "What is the tagline of Sony ?",
        answer: "Make Believe"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question:
          "At what price did Apple stock close today? Full points for +-$5",
        answer: "~289 +/- 5"
      },
      {
        points: 500,
        question: "What are the colors of each letter in google?",
        answer: "G-blue, o- red; o-yellow, g-blue, l-green, e- red"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    category: "America",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "How many stars do the American flag have ?",
        answer: "50"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "Who was opponent of Barak Obama during election ?",
        answer: "John McCain"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "List three states that honour name of famous man ?",
        answer:
          "Delaware (For the British Governer of Virginia, Thomas West Baron De La Warr) <br/> Georgia (For George II of England) <br/> Louisiana (For Louis XIV of France) <br/> New York (Duke of York and Albany) <br/> North and South Carolina (For Endlands Charles I) <br/> Pennsylvania (For Admiral Sir Williams Penn, the father of William Penn) <br/> and Washington (For George washington) <br/>"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question:
          "Which one letter of the alphabet does not appear in the names of any of the fifty states ?",
        answer: "Q"
      },
      {
        points: 500,
        question:
          "Barak Obama is the 44th President of USA, which number Abraham Lincoln was ?",
        answer: "16th"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    category: "India",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "Who is the current Finance Minister of India ?",
        answer: "Nirmala Sitharaman"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "Who wrote national song of India ?",
        answer: "Bankin Chandra Chatterjee"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question:
          "Rabindranath Tagore was awarded first Nobel Prize for which literature ?",
        answer: "Geetanjali"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question:
          "Who is the first India individual to get Gold Medal in Olympics ?",
        answer:
          "Abhinav Bindra for 10m Air Rifle at 2008 Summer Olympics Bejing"
      },
      {
        points: 500,
        question: "Name any 9 Prime Ministers of India ?",
        answer:
          "Jawaharlal Nehru, Gulzarilal Nanda*, Lal Bahadur Shastri, Indira Gandhi*, Morarji Desai, Charan Singh, Rajiv Gandhi, V.P. Singh, Chandra Shekhar, P.V. Narasimha Rao, Atal Bihari Vajpayee*, H.D. Deve Gowda, Inder K. Gujral, Manmohan Singh, Narendra Modi+"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    category: "US SPORTS",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "Which team lost in the Super Bowl in 2020 ?",
        answer: "San Francisco 49ers"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "Who holds the record for most 3 pointers in a season?",
        answer: "Steph Curry threw 402 3-pointers in 2015-2016 season"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "Which team has won the most superbowls? How many ?",
        answer: "Pittsburgh Steelers and New England Patriots"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question:
          "Who has won the most grand slam for mens single tennis? How many?",
        answer: "Roger Federer, 20 grand slams"
      },
      {
        points: 500,
        question:
          "In Formulae one, who has won most championship and how many ?",
        answer: "Michael Schumacher has won 7 championship"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    category: "Riddles",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question:
          "I used to fill rooms but now I am a tower, I can stay put or I can travel far. What am I ?",
        answer: "Computer"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question:
          "We hurt without moving. We poison without touching. We bear the truth and the lies. We are not to be judged by our size. What we are ?",
        answer: "Words"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "What always eats but is always hungry ?",
        answer: "Fire"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question:
          "It takes one word to separate them, otherwise they are inseparable. What are they ?",
        answer: "	Your lips"
      },
      {
        points: 500,
        question: "What goes up and down but never moves ?",
        answer: "Stairs"
      }
    ]
  }
];
